# Sherilyn A. Moline

Tampa, Florida ◆ Phone (813) 786-0525

E-mail: <a href="mailto:smoline@gmail.com">smoline@gmail.com</a> Portfolio: <a href="https://smoline.github.io">https://smoline.github.io</a>

Github: https://qithub.com/smoline + Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/smoline/

#### **WEB APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER**

Team oriented, quality minded, and motivated Ruby on Rails Developer with a solid record of accomplishments emphasizing training and development management in a highly competitive, rapidly growing industry. Demonstrated leadership, problem solving, and planning skills resulting in an integrated system of creative, timely, and practical programs.

## Additional strengths:

Ruby & Sinatra CSS **Problem Solving** Ruby on Rails Sass Communicating MVC Team Building JavaScript **Agile Development** React Researching Postgresgl **Troubleshooting** Typescript

**PostGIS** GraphQL Training

## PROFESSIONAL ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Worked in a Team of Ruby on Rails Developers. Using github the team created a silent auction web application using Rails 5.0, Ruby 2.4, bcrypt, OmniAuth, and Shrine. Using Agile Development we delivered a mvp with time to spare. Result: Delivered a customizable web application that could be used at any number of Fundraising Galas. The client was pleased.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Junior Full-Stack Software Developer, Spatial Networks

September 2017 - Present

Worked on a team of talented engineers to design and develop a custom internal web application. Personally worked on all parts utilizing many tools, including Ruby & Sinatra, GraphQL, Ruby on Rails, React and Typescript.

## Ruby on Rails Program Graduate, The Iron Yard

March 2017 - June 2017

Attended 12-week intensive back-end engineering course designed to give the students the tools and experience needed to enter a career as a junior web applications developer

## President, Moline Services, Inc.

January 2011 - March 2017

- Business support company providing professional services on a contract basis to small businesses and sole practitioner law firms.
- Including administrative support, office management, professional photography, and computer and network support.

## Living in Germany

August 2009 - January 2011

## Office Manager, West Coast Family Practice

April 2007 - August 2009

Provided administrative support to the owner of the practice, including creating procedures for new web based insurance pre-authorizations, and eligibility checks. Researched the new market of EMR software for our practice upgrade.

## **EDUCATION / TRAINING / CERTIFICATIONS**

**Bachelor of Science Degree in Management Information Systems University of South Florida** 

Tampa, FL - 2008

Ruby on Rails Program Graduate, The Iron Yard

St.Petersburg, FL - 2017